Um, so, uh, really excited about the
players we've added so far. Um, I think
Andrew said this to you guys, but going
into this off seasonason,
um, I think he stated we would pretty
heavily invest on this side of the
football. So, I think between um, some
of our acquisitions in the off season
and then, you know, these first three
picks, which, you know, not necessarily
how we thought it would play out, um, it
sort of just matches that theme. I think
what's beautiful about it is all three
of these guys, it's not something that
we felt like we reached for. Um, you
know, we made the trade back in with our
first pick and showed a lot of patience
uh with the next two and still got two
really really good players. So excited
about the group. Um, still have a lot of
work to do with two picks today as it
sits right now and um, you know, ready
to go. So with that, I'll take
questions.
>> It's it's kind of unusual to go back to
back wide receiver. you guys had all
night to think about this pick. Was he
prominent all night?
>> Yeah, I think it's just like I said as
as we said as we took a step back when
as all teams do um when the first round
ends and and look at your board, it it
sort of just, you know, stuck out to us.
Like I said, you know, we didn't
necessarily plan to take two receivers
back to back, but we also uh couldn't
ignore value and again wanted to make
sure that we invested on offense, gave
Todd and the offensive coaches uh the
resources they need to work with. and
and I mean the two players not only fit
that bill, but they they complement each
other and the room uh really really
well.
>> Almost like stealing getting Denzel at
that point.
>> I mean, I would I wouldn't say that, but
we definitely are excited. Like I said,
we you know, we had to show patience uh
cuz you know, you just get antsy when
you see a guy that you think has a ton
of ability. you know, he's big, he has
great hands, um, you know, very subtle,
sneaky speed, uh, and just really really
compleiments things that we we have in
that room right now, and you just have
to exude exude some some patience and
allow it to come to you and and so we're
excited that, you know, we necessarily
have to give up any resources to get a
player of his caliber.
>> What do these two picks say, Glenn,
about the way you guys assessed the wide
receiver room after 2025? Yeah, I think
it it it doesn't necessarily only speak
to the room, but also just speaks to the
two players. Um Casey's really
explosive. He's really talented. We love
what he can do with the football. Um and
then Denzel, you know, almost 6'4, 215.
Um very physical, competitive, and has
great hands. So, I I think it's it's
it's just as much about what we're
adding. And we're always talking about
it's it's you know, this is a team
building exercise, not a player
acquisition exercise. and we're happy
with with the the two skill sets that we
added
>> in terms of
>> Go ahead. Go ahead. You can go.
>> Okay. Like you mentioned with his size
and the 50/50 ball ability that he has,
like how much are you guys hoping that
he can be an immediate sort of red zone
threat as as a
>> Look, I all these guys
find their role at different times. What
we think he has is a great foundation.
Um and it's those different skill sets
that you spoke to. Um, but we just, you
know, we trust Todd uh and Travis and
and the rest of the offensive staff, CJ
in his room to to put them in the right
spot. And what our biggest focus was
like, hey, let's give them as much
talent, um, as much versatility and and
allow them to do their jobs.
>> What about the room now in general,
>> kind of talk about what how wellrounded?
>> Yeah, I think that's a fair question. At
the end of the day, we we you know, we
talk about this. We want to add
competition, you know, so so if you want
to be one of the best offenses, a top
tier offense in the NFL, you know, we
want the cream to rise to the top. And
so, um, you know, we definitely believe
we have talent in the room. Jerry Judy
is still a talent NFL player, but, um,
we're also going to not be complacent
and push ourselves to keep making sure
that we have what we need to be the type
of offense we want to. There was uh
reports uh the beginning of the night
about the Browns talking about moving up
in this round. Uh if that's true, was it
for Boston or someone else?
>> I mean, I can't speak specifically to
what you're saying. I mean, we there's
multiple conversations going on. I mean,
we had conversations about every
direction, you know, moving up, sitting
still, moving back. So, I think that's
just a part of, you know, managing, you
know, our position on the board and and
trying to get a feel for what what's
happening in front of us and behind us.
So, I mean, like I said, I I don't know
specifically what you're talking about,
but yeah, I mean, we're we're we're
always on the phone. I probably have to
go back up and get on the phone again.
Um, so that's just a part of it. Tony,
>> the collaboration like with, you know,
Coach Monk and we saw the video, you
know, wanting a fist bump from Andrew
after making the Boston pick, but, you
know, you worked with Kevin for six
years and now you're you're working with
Todd. just what what's that
collaboration been like?
>> Yeah. Know, I think um I think Todd, as
as you all probably know or are getting
a sense of, he's he's very direct and
he's very clear about what he wants and
what he needs. I think you have a good
sense of how each skill set will fit
into um the system and and the scheme.
And so, uh, throughout the process in
the spring, just across all the
receivers and a lot of the offensive
players, you know, I thought our
offensive coaches gave us a really good
picture of one, what we needed. Um, and
then also two, just as a respect to each
player, um, how they would use them. And
that just makes it a lot clearer for
Andrew and just our staff as a group to
walk into it saying, "Hey, if we take
this player here or if we take this
specific player, this is how they're
going to be deployed in our offense."
And feel good about it, you know? And so
I think he gave us a good picture for
both players, KC and and and um Denzo.
>> I know that you haven't you've invested
in receiver in other ways, right? Trade,
but this is the highest this regime has
taken for receiver, let alone two. Was
there something different
philosophically or in the approach this
draft that led you to to receiver so
high?
>> Honestly, no. You know, like you one,
you always step back and assess what you
can do better, you know, just within the
job. So yeah, you know, we definitely
looked at just across all our picks. Um,
you know, and then we do that every
year, how can we be better, what do we
miss, what do we hit on, etc. But, um,
you know, some of it is one, you know,
we just had higher picks, you know, for
the second year in a row. Uh, and then
it's also just the quality of the
players that we were sitting and looking
at, um, at this spot. So, I wouldn't say
there was a wholesale uh, change to how
we approached it, but you definitely
have to step back and assess yourself.
So,
>> was Boston at all in discussion at 24?
>> I mean, I won't I'm not going to get
into to that. I think, you know, I don't
want to make it a Casey versus Boston
thing. Um,
>> yeah. Yeah. What it is is we trusted the
board. Um, you know, we we think a lot
about Denzel's talent and his ability. I
think a lot of teams probably had him
with a with a first round grade or
really high up. So, you know, we're just
excited that we had the chance to still
get them where we're sitting at.
>> You were going through everything and
the, you know, simulations of your
board. You can try to predict as best
you can following your data and
everything, but how surprised were you
that Denzel felt to you guys right there
and you get your two big wide receivers
that are rated high back to back?
>> Uh, I mean to your point, you can
simulate it as much as you can and we do
I mean we probably spent four plus hours
going through a number of iterations and
you still don't get through all of them,
right? you you still can't uh
100% pinpoint how it's going to play
out. There's probably a few picks in the
first round that even with those number
of iterations that we we went through,
you know, sort of caught us off guard.
So, we try to get as close as possible
and and I think what it does help us do
is have good answers to the test when
they come and so, hey, if we do get a
scenario that's within this this
ballpark, this is how we would play it
out. And I think this is close to maybe
one or two of them that we work through.
Um, it was just just glad we got him,
you know,
>> being in a situation where you have
Casey and Denzel.
>> Did I Did we ever envision it?
>> Sure. Yeah, I think we did envision it,
you know, uh, to tell you that that we
were very certain that it would happen.
I don't I don't know that we could tell
you that, but we definitely It's
definitely something you you think about
just in terms of how you build the team,
how you build the roster, you know, when
you get to pick 39, is this something
you would do where you take two
receivers back to back?
he was here. What did you kind of get to
talk to and see his reaction?
>> So, is it was pretty interesting because
both he and Casey were together, you
know, and so um you know, you have now I
look back both guys are sitting at
dinner and you're getting to know the
two different personalities and getting
to understand uh who they are as humans
and young men and so much about their
life. And I mean, Denzel's um academic
all Big 10. Um you know, an exceptional
kid, you know, loves the game and and
has a lot of head in his future. Same
thing with Casey. Just just hilarious,
funny, a lot of, you know, a lot of
energy, but also very competitive and
just when you spoke to football things,
he definitely, you know, flips a switch
and and you love to see that about him.
So, uh, looking back, like I said, to
the question that was just asked,
couldn't have envisioned that both
players as we sit there at dinner would
be on our roster, but but it's also a
thing that I'm not not mad about.
>> Where was that dinner?
>> It's just our 30 visits. Yeah. So, as
when we take him out to eat,
>> I know a lot's been talked about Casey's
ability on point returns, but Denzel can
also
>> Yeah, he did.
>> I mean, just how much, you know, did
that kind of add add value to
>> We It's in the back of our minds. We
know it, right? like there's it just
adds it's an added luxury to have
players who can you know with with the
constraints of of the 53man roster and
the guys you can have active to have
someone especially with his dimensions
and build to go back and field punts
like it's you know we're definitely um
fortunate that he also can do that our
focus is on his ability at receiver same
thing with KC um and but again it is it
is an added bonus I should have
mentioned that earlier but that's a good
good point
>> everyone assume that offensive line by
receiver in the first round were the top
priorities and obviously that's the
direction you want. Now Andrew Barry
mentioned yesterday he expects this to
be a volume draft for you guys once they
bring in a pretty good size rookie class
or do you feel like now you guys are in
a spot where you can kind of start
stacking the roster? You don't
necessarily have to maybe zero in on
needs
a much maybe as you might have in the
first round.
>> Yeah, I hope so. Also, I mean, I
wouldn't say we we, you know, were we're
were cornered into to zero in on these
as well with the first couple, you know,
like again, we end up taking two
receivers, but uh we have eight picks, I
believe, and um we have two more tonight
at minimum. And I think it is an
opportunity for us to just continue to
add guys who will come in and compete um
at in different roles on different sides
of the football on both sides of the
football. So, uh, yeah, it it was
important for us not to to move too many
picks because we want the volume. Um,
and and we felt like we we needed it.
So, uh, we definitely are excited about
the position that we're in after having
three picks in the first, you know, in
the top 50 and still with eight more to
go. It's it's pretty exciting. when when
you guys hired Todd when he first got
here and he kind of talked to you about
what his sort of vision was for the
offense. Not that you could predict that
what exactly what's going to happen on
on draft night like you mentioned. Um
but is this like pretty close to in
terms of the resources you guys have
used what that kind of vision what you
guys thought that vision could be in
terms of addressing the offensive line,
addressing wide receiver?
>> Sure. But I also think like the the
number one thing and I think you guys
may have heard him say this is nothing
getting in the way of winning. And I
think he approaches coaching and and
calling the game that way. Uh he will
have two tight ends on the field, three
tight ends on the field, uh four
receivers, uh different packages, run,
you know, run the quarterback. Um get
feed feed the guy who's having a great
game. I think Todd is is so diverse in
his approach and so open-minded when it
comes to how to move the football down
the field and score points because at
the end of the day, that's what we're
trying to do. Uh it from a 30,000 foot
view, it just opened up our opportunity
across all the players in the draft
because you just know um you're not
necessarily pigeonholed into it has to
be X skill set, X build, X makeup.
really like, hey, have a good idea of
how we want to use this guy and and and
Todd will take it from there. So, it was
more so probably from that lens as
opposed to the specific like skill sets
at receiver or running back or tight end
or O line if that answers.
>> Appreciate you.